//Creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What color are minions?",
        answer: "Yellow",
        options: [
            "Blue",
            "Orange",
            "Yellow",
            "Red"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following isn't a minion?",
        answer: "Gru",
        options: [
            "Gru",
            "Bob",
            "Stuart",
            "Kevin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What language do the minions speak??",
        answer: "Minionese",
        options: [
            "English",
            "Mayonaise",
            "Milanese",
            "Minionese"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What do minions like to eat?",
        answer: "Bananas",
        options: [
            "Oranges",
            "Vegetables",
            "Apples",
            "Bananas"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What's the minions' second favorite food?",
        answer: "Spaghetti",
        options: [
            "Fish",
            "Chips and bananas",
            "Spaghetti",
            "Napkin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which movie did the Minions not appear in?",
        answer: "Minions 4",
        options: [
            "especiable Me 2",
            "Minions 4",
            "Minions",
            "Despicable Me 3"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which is the first minion to be mentioned by name?",
        answer: "Kevin",
        options: [
            "Dave",
            "Alfonso Garbonzo",
            "Stuart",
            "Kevin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is an enemy of the minions?",
        answer: "Balthazar Bratt",
        options: [
            "Agnes Gru",
            "Balthazar Bratt",
            "Pierre Coffin",
            "Pizza Platt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which Minion tried to eat a fire hydrant?",
        answer: "Stuart",
        options: [
            "Stuart",
            "Kevin",
            "ark",
            "Bob"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who is the only minion with braces?",
        answer: "Otto",
        options: [
            "Mark",
            "Stuart",
            "Ortho",
            "Otto"
        ]
    },
];